<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Bits, Bytes, and Things That Compile in the Night (first post)</title><link>https://ajsmith.github.io/</link><description></description><atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://ajsmith.github.io/categories/first-post.xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 19:56:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>https://getnikola.com/</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>init();</title><link>https://ajsmith.github.io/posts/init/</link><dc:creator>Alex Smith</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welp, it looks like I'm starting a new blog. I guess I'll start off with a few
words about what I aim to cover here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a blog about my personal adventures in software engineering. It will
likely include lessons learned from the things I work on, announcements related
to public projects I'm part of, opinions on various technology topics, and
maybe some writings about cool things I've been doing in my personal time
(mostly geeky things, I'm sure). My goal is to make it informative and fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is as much for me as it is for you. The exercise of writing helps to
better organize my thoughts, and the things I write will capture and preserve
my thoughts much longer than my memory can hold. Of course I hope that others
will find value or usefulness in the things I write, but I also hope to make
this something worthwhile for me to come back to and reflect on past projects
and experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So with that, I welcome you to my little corner of the blerg-o-sphere. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>first post</category><guid>https://ajsmith.github.io/posts/init/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>